A Guide to the Papers of Paul T. David 1954-1959
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of Paul T. David 1954-1959
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
12793-f
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was given to the University of Virginia Library as a gift on July 13, 1962.
Contents List
- The Politics of National Party Conventions 1954-1959
  - Chapter 1 with Corrections 1955-1959 (Box 1)
  - Chapter 2 with Corrections 1955-1959 (Box 1)
  - Chapter 3 with Corrections 1956-1959 (Box 1)
  - Chapter 4 with Corrections 1956-1959 (Box 1)
  - Chapter 5 with Corrections 1959 (Box 1)
  - Chapter 6 with Corrections 1959 (Box 1)
  - Chapter 7 with Corrections 1956-1959 (Box 1)
  - Chapter 8 with Corrections 1957-1958 (Box 2)
  - Chapter 9 with Corrections 1954-1958 (Box 2)
  - Chapter 10 with Corrections 1955-1958, 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Chapter 11 with Corrections 1958 (Box 2)
  - Chapter 12 with Corrections 1958, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Chapter 13 with Corrections 1954-1958 (Box 3)
  - Chapter 14 with Corrections 1954-1958, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Chapter 15 with Corrections 1959 (Box 4)
  - Chapter 16 with Corrections 1955-1959, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Chapter 17 with Corrections 1959 (Box 4)
  - Chapter 18 with Corrections 1959 (Box 4)